Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1965-2007; Accession 2009-M-018
  - Editorial files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research
    - Veatch, Robert M., 1974-1991 (Box 22, Folder 33-34)
    - Vollmann, Jochen, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Waggoner, William, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Walker, Paulette, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Walters, LeRoy, 1975-1987 (Box 22, Folder 38-39)
    - Watkins, Judy, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Weijer, Charles, 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 41-42)
    - Weir, Robert, 1990-1998 (Box 22, Folder 43-44)
    - Wells, James, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Wells, Robert, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Whitbeck, Caroline, 1983-1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wichman, Allison, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Wigodsky, Herman, 1980-1991 (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - Professional files
    - Reviews of writings of others, 1988-2002 (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
      - Bioethics at Yale (grant), 2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Expert testimony
      - Statement of the Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC) on Institutional Review Boards, Presented to the Subcommittee on Human Resources of the Committee on Government Reform and Oversight, United States House of Representatives, 1998 June 11 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Conference binders
      - Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices for Disease Control and Prevention Influenza Working Group Meeting, 2005 January 36-27 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Annual Institutional Review Board (IRB) Conference, Communication: The Cornerstone of an Ethical Research Environment, 2004 October 29-31 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
      - Anthrax Vaccine Adsorbed: Human Reactogenicity and Immunogenicity Trial to Address Change of Route in Administration and Dose Reduction
        - Application, 2001 September 13 (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - Clinical Protocol, Version 4, 2002 May 15 (Box 24, Folder 16-18)
        - Procedures Manual, 2002 April 18 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
        - Appendices, Circa 2002 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
      - Bayer Institute for Health Care Communication Board of Directors Manual, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Belmont Revisited, 1999 April 16-18 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - CDC External Review Group for the Institutional Review Board (IRB), 2000 March 24 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Clinical Trials on Trial: Protecting Human Subjects of Research (Staff Training in Extramural Programs-STEP), 2001 May 17 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Human Tissue/Specimen Banking Working Group: Background Material, 2004 June 21 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
        - National Bioethics Advisory Commission. Reports [commercially produced], 1997-2001; 1 (Box 25-10)
      - IRB 101: Biomedical Resource Guide, 2003 December 4 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - IRB 101: Training, 2005 February 25 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - IRB Educational and Networking Symposium
        - 2003 October 28 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - 2006 December 12 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - IRB Guidebook, 1983 December 5 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - IRBs and New Approaches: Assessing, Evaluating, Discarding, and Moving Forward, 2001 December 3-4 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
      - International Research Ethics: Building Collaboration and Communication, 2005 December 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - 2005 Annual HRPP Conference: Ethics and Trust Across Boundaries: Educational Resources [commercially produced], 2005 December 3-6; 1 (Box 26.1)
      - Johns Hopkins Medicine Research Compliance: Challenges and Opportunities, 2001 May 6-7 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Joint Meeting of the Ethics Subcommittee of the Advisory Committtee to the Director, CDC and CDC's Public Health Ethics Committee, 2006 September 14-15 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Journal of Empirical Research on Human Research Ethics (JEHRE): An Educational Conference on Creative Ethical Problem Solving in Human Research: Challenges and Solutions for Researchers and Ethics Committees, 2006 July 28 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - National Human Research Protections Advisory Committee
        - 2000 December 20-21 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - 2001 April 9-10 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - 2001 July 30-31 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
        - 2002 July 30-31 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Program for the Study of Health Care Relationships: Expert Panel Members Information Packet, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - President's Council on Bioethics, 2006 April 20-21 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Public Responsibility in Medicine and Research (PRIM&R) IRB Conference, 2002 November 18-19 (Box 26, Folder 12-14)
      - RAND Corporation: Ethical Principles in Social-Behavioral Research on Terrorism: Probing the Parameters, 2007 January 10 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Reclaiming the Belmont Principles for Human Research Protections: Looking Back to Move Forward (18th Annual Meeting of ARENA and PrIM&R's Annual IRB Conference), 2003 December 6-7 (Box 26, Folder 16-17)
      - World Health Organization (WHO) Meeting on the Prevention of Craniofacial Anomalies, 2001 May 24-26 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
      - Yale International AIDS Summer Institute: The Ethics of International AIDS Research: Contemporary Practices and Controversies, 2002 June 5-10 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Publications
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS)
      - On Being a Scientist, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - On Being a Scientist: Responsible Conduct in Research, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, 1955-2014; Accession 2016-M-0064; 9.78; (22 boxes)
  Accession 2016-M-0064 contains student records and is closed until 1 January 2089 by Yale Corporation regulations http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives.
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  Accession 2016-M-0064 contains material related to Robert J. Levine's research and teaching at the Yale University School of Medicine. Includes research files, scholarly articles and writings, correspondence with Yale faculty and students, correspondence and consultations with medical professionals outside Yale, and office files on individuals and organizations.
  The material is divided into three groupings: research files, correspondence, and office files.
  - Research files
    - Adjuvant therapy with Tamoxifen vs. Placebo in older (65 years) postmenopausal patients with stage II breast cancer, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Blue Ribbon Committee, 1970–1972 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Carcinoid syndrome, Circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Comparison of epidural saline placement and epidural blood placement in the treatment of post-lumbar puncture headache, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Continuing education committee, 1970–1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Data on inhibitors in vivo-rats, 1966–1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Diamine oxidase protocol, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Donaldson committee, 1979–1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Drug MK-785, 1966–1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Epi test protocol, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ethical and human value implications of science and technology proposal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ethics and regulation of clinical research, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Informed Consent in Human Research: Ethical and Legal Aspects, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Institutional Review Board study, Northwestern University, 1980–1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Mentally infirm research, 1978–1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - NSD-1055 protocols, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - PHS-NIH individual project reports, 1961–1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Problem of Personhood, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Protocols for clinical research studies, 1964–1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Serum enzyme changes after intramuscular injections of Bupivacaine and Procaine, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Social Contexts Influence Ethical Considerations of Research, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence
    - Amato, Joseph, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Amatruda Jr., Thomas T., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - American Oil Company, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Antonita, Marie, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ashman, Bert, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bandyopadhyay, Sandip Kumar, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bayard, Edwin, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Beeson, Paul B., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bell, Norman, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bernstein, Daniel, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bertino, Joseph, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Black, Henry, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Blair, A.M.J.N., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Boshell, Buris R., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Boulos, Badi M., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Brennan, John, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Broitman, Selwyn, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Brunjes, Shannon, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Bursten, Stuart, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Cahow, Elton, 1981–1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Call, Edward, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Clapper, Muir, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Cleland, Nona, 1964–1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Code, Charles F., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Cohen, Gerald, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Cohen, Phin, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Combs, Joseph, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Department of Public Health, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut State Board of the Healing Arts, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Coren, Simon, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Clarence, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Dineen, Elaine, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Drayer, Dennis, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Eisenfeld, Arnold, 1965–1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Eppinger, Eugene, 1961–1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - F.A. David Company, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Finger, Barbara S., 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Foltz, E. L., 1966–1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Freedman, Daniel X., 1965–1993 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    - Friedman, Abraham, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Gaffney, Thomas E., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Garattini, Silvio, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Genel, Myron, 1985–1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Gertner, Sheldon B., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Giarman, Nicholas J., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Gillespie, Elizabeth, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Goldfinger, Stephen, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Gordon, Robert S., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Gosselink, Paul, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Goth, Andres, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Grennell, Kathy, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Hait, William N., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Handschumacher, Robert E., 1966–1968 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Hayes, Kay, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Helton, Arthur C., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Hershatter, Belle, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Jervis, Helen, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Johnson, Carl, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Kelly, Gordon, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Kenney, James D., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Kremzner, Leon, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Landsberg, Lewis, 1963–1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Levine, Macy I., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Levine, Robert A., 1965–1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Lobuglio, Albert F., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Magee, Donal F., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Matheke, Cynthia, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - McGuigan, James, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Meiss, Edwin R., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Modic, Robert A., 1969–1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Mulrow, Patrick, 1965–1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - National Institute of Health, 1962–1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - O'Brien, William, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Och, Norman W., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Olayen C., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Olsen, Inger, 1961–1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Pappas, Kathy, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Paul, Fred, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Pettinger, William, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Phair, John P., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Plaisted, Robert, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Plotz, Charles M, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Porter, George H., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Prockop, Darwin J., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Raidbard, Alvin, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Redlich, Frederick, 1967–1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Reidenberg, Marcus, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Ritchie, J. Murdoch, 1968–1972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Rivlin, Richard, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Rodhan, Gerald P., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Rosen, Samuel F., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Sachs, George, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Schimpff, Stephen, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Schwartz, Raphael D., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Senay, Edward C., 1967–1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Spector, Sydney, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Speight, Harold E., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Spiro, Howard, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - St. Marie, Gerald L., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Stead, Eugene A., Jr., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Stern, P., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Sweeney, Paula, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Thayer, Walter, 1965–1969 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Troncale, Frank, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - United States Public Health Service, Local Board No. 4, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - University of Chicago, 1967–1970 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Van Woert, Melvin, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Vendsalu, Aado, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Watts, Doris, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Wick, H., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Williams, Marilyn, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Winter, Thorne, 1964–1965 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Yalon, Joseph, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Zito, Ruben A., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Office files
    - 70th birthday, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Abel Award, pharmacology, 1967–1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Academy of Pharmaceutical Physicians and Investigators, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Adolescent Treatment Network, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Advanced Medical Ethics, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Agich, George, 2002–2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - American Association for Cancer Research, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - American Board of Internal Medicine, 1964–1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1991–1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - American Journal of Bioethics, Circa 2000s (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - American Men of Science, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Public Health Association, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - American Society for Bone and Mineral Research, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - American Society of Law, Medicine, and Ethics, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Amgen Consulting Services Agreement, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Anderson, Susan, 1969–1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Angoff, Nancy R., 1981–1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Annenberg Center for Health Sciences, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Annual Review of Pharmacology, 1967–1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Association of Academic Health Centers Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Association of Clinical Research Professionals European Meeting, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 2002–2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - AstraZeneca, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Baker, C. Bruce, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Baron, Richard, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Beaumont Club, 1969–1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Beaumont Report, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
    - Berkelman, Ruth, Circa 2000s (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Bern, Samuel, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bernhardt, David, 2004–2006 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bernstein, Peter, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Bikson, Tora, Circa 2000s (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Bindet, Circa 2000s (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bioethics and Biodefence meeting, Washington D.C., 2007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Bioethics Digest, 1976–1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Blake Award, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bondy, Philip K., 1968–1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Bower, Bruce, Circa 2000s (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Brennan, Troyen, 1979–1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Brennan, Troyen, 1979–1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bristol-Myers Squibb Pharmaceutical Research Institute, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Buri, Bo, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Calabresi, Paul, 1964–1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cassell, Eric, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Center for Disease Control, 2005–2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS, 1999–2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Chadwick, Gary, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Chan, Carlyle Hung-lun, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Changsha, China, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Chapo, Andrea, research assistant, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Childress, Jim, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - China, 2002–2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - China trip, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cist, David, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Clark, Chalmers, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Clinical editors, 1970–1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Clinical research papers, 1980–1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cole, Douglas R., recommendations, 1971–1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Congressional record, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1995–2012 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Connecticut medical license, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Constantopoulos, George, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Contract Research Ethics Organization, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Coughlin-Beauchamp article agreement, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences, 1990–2005 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Covington v. Kennedy Krieger Institute, et al., 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Dalhousie University, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Data and Safety Monitoring Board, Division of AIDS, National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, National Institute of Health (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - DeBonis, Linda, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - DeFelice, Stephen (Doctornaut Act), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Department of Energy, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1970–1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Donaghue Medical Research Foundation, 2002–2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Drug control bill, 1969–1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Duke University health center, 2003–2004 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dunbar, Jackie, University of Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Eastern Cooperative Oncology Group, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Einstein Institute for Science, Health and the Courts, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ellenberg, Susan, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Emory University, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Employee financial forms, Circa 1970s (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Encyclopedia of the Social and Behavioral Sciences proofs, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Encyclopedia of Bioethics, Bioethical Research, 1975–1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Encyclopedia of Bioethics, 1976–1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Encyclopedia of Bioethics, 1995–2012 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Engel, Linda W., The Science of the Placebo, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Epelbaum, Jennifer, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ethical Aspects of Avian Influenza Pandemic Preparedness symposium, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ethics and Regulation of Clinical Research, 2002–2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Farley, Margaret, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Fellowship position/post-doc rejection letters, 1973–1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Flather-Morgan, Alexandra, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Fleischman, Alan, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Ford, Ann, case study, Circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Forman, Lesley Nan, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Forum on Medicine, 1977–1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Fost, Norm, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Freedman, Barbara, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - French, Shannon E., 2006 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Future of Medicine Center, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Gandhi, Rupali, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Geertsma, Mary Anne, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Gordon, Jeffrey Ivan, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Gorovitz, Samuel, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Grady, Christine, promotion, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Grinnell, Fred, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gryboski, Joyce, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Hammond, Leon, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Hanson, Helena, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The Hastings Center, 2000–2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Health Improvement Institute, 2004–2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Heisler, Seymour, McGill University, Circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hereke rug purchase, 1988–1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Hesse, Katherine, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Hirsch, Larry, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Holder, Angela, recommendations, 1975–1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Hopkins, Patricia, salary, 1975–1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Huang, Paul, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Indiana University lectures, 2001–2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Institute for Community Research, 2001–2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Institute of Medicine, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 2002–2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Internal Medicine student evaluations, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - International Encyclopedia of the Social and Behavioral Sciences, 2000–2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Jewelry, 1984–2001 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Johns Hopkins, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Josephine Apartments, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kass, Nancy, promotion recommendation, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Katz, Martin D., 1980–1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Kettering Medical Center, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Klitzman, Robert, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Kramer, Laura, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Landau, Peter, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Lantos, John, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Lasagna, Louis, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Lavery, Jim, 2004–2010 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Lebacqz, Karen, 1976–1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Lebacqz, Karen, 1976–1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lederer, Susan, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Levine, Amy and John, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levine, Ben, Circa 2000s (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Levine, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Levine, Elizabeth (Eckerd College), 1981–1985 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Levine, Robert J., personal file, 1958–1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Levine, Robert J., photographs, Circa 1960s (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lewis Child and Adolescent Psychiatry 4th edition, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, John, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, Melvin, 2002–2007 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Liebman, Theodor S., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Lowery, Julie, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - MacLean Center for Clinical Medical Ethics, Controversies in Research Ethics, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Manchester, William, 1973–1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Maratchi, Diane, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Marcy, Theodore W., recommendation letters, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marks, J.W., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Martensen, Robert, 2003–2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Josefina Vega, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Medical Ethics course, 1980–1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Menkes, Jeffrey S., recommendation letters, 1971–1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Menstrual Cycle and Adolescent Health Conference, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 12)